let detective_operations_questions_repo = {
    "1":{
            "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
            "question": "Once a document has been submitted via chain of command, it becomes a historical document.",
            "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "2":{
            "questionType": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What should be done if additional information is obtained after the initial Follow-Up Investigation has been submitted?",
            "answer1": "Add the information to the original E-document",
            "answer2": "Create a new 03.14.00 as a Supplemental Investigation",
            "answer3": "Submit the additional information as a handwritten document",
            "answer4": "Discard the additional information",
            "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "3": {
            "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
            "question": "Which of the following statements about E-documents are true based on the given paragraph?",
            "answer1": "E-documents are usually submitted via a computer or word processor",
            "answer2": "Handwritten documents are no longer acceptable",
            "answer3": "A document that has been submitted via chain of command becomes a historical document",
            "answer4": "Additional information obtained after the initial Follow-Up Investigation must be documented on a new 03.14.00 as a Supplemental Investigation",
            "answer5": "Supplemental documents must be added to an E-document that has previously been submitted and routed through chain of command",
            "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer3", "answer4"]
        },
    "4": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Follow-Up Investigation, Form 03.14.00?",
        "answer1": "To record additional information and results of an investigation after completion of the original crime or incident report.",
        "answer2": "To correct information on the original report.",
        "answer3": "To report the progress in the investigation.",
        "answer4": "To change the case status of the original report.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
        },
    "5": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The Follow-Up Investigation, Form 03.14.00, is an integral part of the Department's reporting system.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "6": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following forms can be changed the case status of using the Follow-Up Investigation, Form 03.14.00?",
        "answer1": "Arrest Report, Form 05.02.00",
        "answer2": "Death Investigation, Form 03.11.00",
        "answer3": "Injury Investigation, Form 03.15.00",
        "answer4": "Missing/Found Persons Investigation, Form 03.16.00",
        "answer5": "Non-traffic Notice to Appear, Form 05.02.02",
        "answer6": "Investigative Report, Form 03.01.00",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer5"]
        },
    "7": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Which of the following forms can be corrected using the Follow-Up Investigation, Form 03.14.00?",
        "answer1": "Disposition of Arrest and Court Action, Form 05.09.00",
        "answer2": "Injury Investigation, Form 03.15.00",
        "answer3": "Investigator's Final Report, Form 05.10.00",
        "answer4": "Missing/Found Persons Investigation, Form 03.16.00",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "8": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The Follow-Up Investigation, Form 03.14.00, can be used to report a final disposition of a case.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "9": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following forms can be used to book additional property related to a previously completed Property Report?",
        "answer1": "Disposition of Arrest and Court Action, Form 05.09.00",
        "answer2": "Injury Investigation, Form 03.15.00",
        "answer3": "Investigator's Final Report, Form 05.10.00",
        "answer4": "Missing/Found Persons Investigation, Form 03.16.00",
        "answer5": "Property Report, Form 10.01.00",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer5"]
        },
    "10": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Which of the following special follow-up reports can be used in lieu of a Form 03.14.00 for a homicide investigation?",
        "answer1": "Murder Investigation Progress Report",
        "answer2": "Victim's Supplemental Property Loss, Form 03.04.00",
        "answer3": "Victim's Supplemental Financial Loss Report, Form 03.05.00",
        "answer4": "Narcotic's Report, Form 3.19.00",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
        },
    "11": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "A Narrative Supplemental, CHP Form 556 or a Traffic Collision-Status Report, Form 4 can be used as a follow-up report for a narcotics investigation.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "12": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following forms must be submitted for approval and distributed once completed?",
        "answer1": "Form 03.14.00",
        "answer2": "Murder Investigation Progress Report",
        "answer3": "Victim's Supplemental Property Loss, Form 03.04.00",
        "answer4": "Victim's Supplemental Financial Loss Report, Form 03.05.00",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer4"]
        },
    "13": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "A Follow-up Investigation, Form 03.14.00, is required only when there is a change in the case status.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "14": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a circumstance that merits follow-up investigation according to the Detective Operations Manual?",
        "answer1": "Information which tends to identify or eliminate a known or possible suspect.",
        "answer2": "A significant change in the description of the missing property.",
        "answer3": "The responsibility for investigation of the case is assigned to another division.",
        "answer4": "Information which is not important enough to merit a Form 03.14.00.",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
        },
    "15": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following circumstances would require a Follow-up Investigation, Form 03.14.00, according to the Detective Operations Manual?",
        "answer1": "The original crime or incident is reclassified.",
        "answer2": "A change in the suspect's identity.",
        "answer3": "The responsibility for investigation of the case is transferred to another division.",
        "answer4": "Corrections to the original report(s) are necessary.",
        "answer5": "There is additional property loss.",
        "answer6": "There is a significant change in the description of the missing property.",
        "answer7": "A request for laboratory confirmation of National Integrated Ballistics Information Network (NIBIN) Links is warranted.",
        "answer8": "Missing juvenile cases require a Form 3.14 Follow-Up Investigation progress report to be completed at 30 and 90 days, six months, and one year progress reports.",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4", "answer5", "answer6", "answer7", "answer8"]
        },
    "16": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Follow-up Investigation, Form 03.14.00?",
        "answer1": "To identify the Department employee who cleared the crime",
        "answer2": "To identify the clearance code for the crime",
        "answer3": "To identify the case status of the cleared crime",
        "answer4": "To identify the location of the cleared crime",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
        },
    "17": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The Follow-up Investigation form needs to identify the actual date the crime was solved and/or cleared.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "18": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following is true about the Actual Date Cleared (ADC) field?",
        "answer1": "It allows the Department to differentiate if a crime was cleared in the current year or a prior year",
        "answer2": "It ensures that crime clearance statistics are accurate for the current year",
        "answer3": "It allows the Department to account for clearances that occurred in prior years without affecting the current year's clearance rate",
        "answer4": "It is located to the left of the clearance code in CCAD",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3"]
        },
    "19": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The RHD is the only entity authorized to update CCAD on Cleared Other Homicide Cases.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "20": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The detective supervisor needs to review the original report and any accompanying reports to determine whether a report falls within Category One or Two.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "21": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following are circumstances or significant facts that the detective supervisor must consider when determining whether a report falls within Category One or Two?",
        "answer1": "Named suspect (including moniker) or associate",
        "answer2": "Physical evidence that could identify suspect",
        "answer3": "License number and/or vehicle description",
        "answer4": "Death or injury to victim",
        "answer5": "Amount of property loss (amount is at commanding officer's discretion)",
        "answer6": "Major crime patterns (MO)",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4", "answer5", "answer6"]
        },
    "22": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The presence or absence of any of the factors listed in DOM Volume I, Sections 121.01 through 121.02, means that the case will automatically be assigned to a particular category.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "23": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Which cases fall under Category One - Required Follow-up?",
        "answer1": "All non-criminal reports",
        "answer2": "Reports involving murder, sexual abuse, or serious injury",
        "answer3": "Reports with significant leads and specific circumstances requiring immediate investigation",
        "answer4": "All of the above",
        "correctAnswer": "answer4"
        },
    "24": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "Property reports involving lost, stolen, or wanted firearms are always assigned to a detective from the same division or section.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "25": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which missing juvenile cases are required to be investigated under Category One - Required Follow-up?",
        "answer1": "Cases where the juvenile has been missing for 30 days",
        "answer2": "Cases where the juvenile has been missing for 90 days",
        "answer3": "Cases where the juvenile has been missing for six months",
        "answer4": "Cases where the juvenile has been missing for one year",
        "answer5": "Cases where significant information is received",
        "answer6": "All missing juvenile cases",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4", "answer5"]
        },
    "26": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "A Form 03.14.00 is required for reporting the investigative results/progress of Category One cases.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "27": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "For physical or sexual abuse crimes, when should the Form 03.14.00 be completed?",
        "answer1": "Within 10 working days",
        "answer2": "Within 30 calendar days",
        "answer3": "Within 15 working days",
        "answer4": "Within 45 calendar days",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "28": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "When should a Form 03.14.00 be submitted for non-custody cases?",
        "answer1": "Within 10 working days",
        "answer2": "Within 30 calendar days",
        "answer3": "Within 15 working days",
        "answer4": "Within 45 calendar days",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "29": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "If an arrest is made during the 30 calendar day period for non-custody cases, it becomes an in-custody case.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "30": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "What is/are the exception(s) to the blanket authority to extend due dates?",
        "answer1": "Homicide Manual",
        "answer2": "Manual of Juvenile Procedures",
        "answer3": "Category Two cases",
        "answer4": "Category Three cases",
        "answer5": "Crimes involving theft",
        "answer6": "Crimes involving drugs",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2"]
        },
    "31": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "If a Follow-up Investigation, Form 03.14.00 is not submitted on a Category One case within the required ten or 30 day due date, the case is no longer considered a backlogged case.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "32": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "When are detectives required to investigate Category Two cases?",
        "answer1": "Only when they have spare time after handling all Category One cases",
        "answer2": "Immediately after a Category One case is closed",
        "answer3": "At their discretion, without any priority given to Category One cases",
        "answer4": "Category Two cases are not investigated by detectives",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
        },
    "33": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following situations fall under Category Two cases?",
        "answer1": "Gasoline drive-outs where the theft of gasoline is the only crime involved",
        "answer2": "Annoying or threatening telephone calls with a named suspect",
        "answer3": "Annoying or threatening telephone calls with a specific lead which would direct the detective to the suspect",
        "answer4": "Annoying or threatening telephone calls with an imminent danger to the victim",
        "answer5": "Gasoline drive-outs where the victim does not wish to prosecute",
        "answer6": "Annoying or threatening telephone calls which require immediate investigation",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer3", "answer5"]
        },
    "34": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "Detectives are required to routinely contact Category Two victims.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "35": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What form should be used to document follow-up efforts on a Category Two case if investigated?",
        "answer1": "Form 03.14.00",
        "answer2": "Detective's Case Progress Log, Form 01.44.00",
        "answer3": "Chronological Record, Form 03.11.06",
        "answer4": "None of the above",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
        },
    "36": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The area detective division and specialized detective division commanding officers can use volunteers to contact Category Two victims.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "37": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Should detectives be used to contact Category Two victims?",
        "answer1": "Yes, they should",
        "answer2": "No, they should not",
        "answer3": "It depends on the situation",
        "answer4": "Only if volunteers are not available",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "38": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The category assigned to a report vary between geographic areas due to work load or personnel differences.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "39": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "A case be downgraded once it has been categorized.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "40": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What is the Form number for Follow-up Investigation on Factually Innocent arrestees?",
        "answer1": "Form 03.15.00",
        "answer2": "Form 03.14.00",
        "answer3": "Form 05.10.00",
        "answer4": "Form 01.20.00",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "41": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "Form 05.10.00 can be used in lieu of Form 03.14.00 when there is no corresponding crime or combined crime and arrest.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "42": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The Form 03.14.00 should be completed for minors who have been missing for more than 30 days.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "43": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The Upper Portion of Form 03.14.00 is comprised of the MULTIPLE box through CASE STATUS.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
        },
    "44": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What section of DOM Volume I covers Case Status?",
        "answer1": "Section 151.00",
        "answer2": "Section 152.00",
        "answer3": "Section 160.00",
        "answer4": "Section 151.01",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "45": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which sections are included in the Upper Portion of Form 03.14.00?",
        "answer1": "Multiple Box",
        "answer2": "Date This Report",
        "answer3": "Date Original Report",
        "answer4": "Case Status",
        "answer5": "Sections 151.03 through 151.12",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3"]
        },
    "46": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What should be recorded in the DR Number (Division of Records)?",
        "answer1": "The victim's name",
        "answer2": "The reporting district as reported on the original report",
        "answer3": "The arrestee's name",
        "answer4": "The booking number from the original arrest report",
        "correctAnswer": "answer2"
        },
    "47": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "It is necessary to record the victim's name when the Form 03.14.00 is a follow-up to an arrest report.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "48": {
        "questionType": "selectAllThatApply",
        "question": "Which of the following should be recorded in the Victim/Booked To/Arrestee section?",
        "answer1": "The victim's name",
        "answer2": "The arrestee's name",
        "answer3": "The name to which the property is booked",
        "answer4": "The primary victim's name",
        "answer5": "The names of all additional victims",
        "answer6": "The name of the reporting district",
        "correctAnswer": ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"]
        },
    "49": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "When should the victim's sex, descent, and age be recorded?",
        "answer1": "When making corrections or additions to an arrest report",
        "answer2": "When the Form 03.14.00 is a follow-up to a property report",
        "answer3": "When reclassifying a Investigative Report to Murder",
        "answer4": "When the Form 03.14.00 is a follow-up to a combined crime and arrest report",
        "correctAnswer": "answer3"
        },
    "50": {
        "questionType": "trueOrFalse",
        "question": "The booking number is required for every Form 03.14.00.",
        "correctAnswer": "false"
        },
    "51": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "What should be entered in the PERIOD ORIGINAL REPORT box when using the DCTS assigned tracking number?",
        "answer1": "A number from 1-12 representing a calendar month",
        "answer2": "The division control number assigned to the original report",
        "answer3": "The report number in that month",
        "answer4": "None of the above",
        "correctAnswer": "answer1"
        },
    "52": {
        "questionType": "multipleChoice",
        "question": "Under the WORK FOLDER in DCTS, the INDEX NO. is for the report number in that corresponding month.",
        "correctAnswer": "true"
    }
}